{
    "subject": "Victor_Salva",
    "predicate": "produced",
    "object": "Clownhouse",
    "human_readable": "Victor Salva produced Clownhouse.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.5782175064086914,
            "question": "What is the name of the movie Victor Salva produced?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5538158416748047,
            "question": "Is Victor Salva known for producing movies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5331111550331116,
            "question": "What year was Clownhouse released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38990750908851624,
            "question": "Who directed the movie Clownhouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37169748544692993,
            "question": "Who are some actors that might have been in Clownhouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.29424551129341125,
            "question": "What is known about Victor Salva's filmmaking style?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.25791120529174805,
            "question": "How popular was the movie Clownhouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.25064709782600403,
            "question": "What genre might the movie Clownhouse belong to, given its director?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22789128124713898,
            "question": "Can you name another movie directed by Victor Salva?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2167089581489563,
            "question": "Are there any common themes in Victor Salva's films?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Victor Salva produced Clownhouse.",
            "html": "yago_7078_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name another movie directed by Victor Salva?",
            "html": "yago_7078_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre might the movie Clownhouse belong to, given its director?",
            "html": "yago_7078_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How popular was the movie Clownhouse?",
            "html": "yago_7078_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7078_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7078_105.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7078_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7078_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7078_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7078_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7078_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7078_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7078_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7078_94.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'} \n``` \n\n\nWhile the documents state that Victor Salva wrote and directed *Clownhouse*, they do not mention him as the producer. Michael Danty is listed as the producer in one of the provided text excerpts.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}\n\nExplanation:\n\nThe documents provide information about Victor Salva as the writer and director of Clownhouse, but there is no mention of him producing the film. In fact, the Wikipedia article for Clownhouse mentions Michael Danty and Robin Mortarotti as producers, along with Victor Salva."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: None of the provided documents mention that Victor Salva produced \"Clownhouse.\" The documents state that Victor Salva wrote and directed the film, but there is no information about him being a producer."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}